Rehab Alonizan

Technical Support Specialist

Address: Al-Khobar – Saudi Arabia **Phone:** 966 – 548852708

E-mail: Rehabalonaizan@hotmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rehab-

<u>alonizan-0604091b3/</u>

Technical Support Specialist and CompTIA A+ certified.

Well-versed in assisting users with diverse computer systems, mobile devices, and peripheral equipment problems. Familiar with security standards and usability optimization. Effectively operates autonomously to troubleshoot and fix concerns.

Work History

2021-12 - Technical Support Specialist

Current Namaa World Technology, Khobar

- Recorded and maintained relevant notes for each client and work order.
- Assisted customers in identifying issues and explained solutions to restore service and functionality.
- Explained technical information in clear terms to promote better understanding for non-technical users.
- Documented support interactions for future reference.
- Patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Analyzed issues to identify troubleshooting methods needed for quick remediation.
- Provided high-level technical support by resolving inquiries by phone, e-mail and web consistent with department and team service levels and goals.

2021-06 - Assistant Volunteer

2021-08 Imam Abdulrahman Bin Faisal University, Khobar

- Assist in development of university's alumni recruitment platform.
- Assisting in communicating with university alumni, entering and updating their data in database.
- Checking employee devices on weekly basis, to check for any issues found in devices.

Education

2013-08 - Bachelor's: Computer Information Systems (CIS)

2020-05 Imam Abdulrahman Bin Faisal University - Saudi Arabia

Technical Profile

- Microsoft 365
- Google Drive
- Microsoft Project
- Technical Support

Competencies

- Ticket support system management
- Issue troubleshooting
- Technical Support
- Remote IT Implementation
- Technical issues analysis

Certifications and Achievements

2022-09 CompTIA A+ 2021-06 TOEFL iBT

Languages

- Arabic
- English

Professional Skills

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Task Management
- Communication